// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The year of the foundation of the Womenâ€™s Indian Association (WIA) is",
    answer: "1917",
    options: [
      "1947",
      "1937",
      "1927",
      "1917"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "By the Act of 1858, India was to be governed",
    answer: "In the name of the Crown",
    options: [
      "By the Company",
      "In the name of the Crown",
      "By a Board of Directors",
      "In the name of Governor-General of India"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The Ghadar Party was founded (November 1913) at San Francisco USA by",
    answer: "Lala Har Dayal",
    options: [
      "Madam Bhikaji Cama",
      "Lala Har Dayal",
      "Shyamji Krishana Verma",
      "Both (a) and (b) above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "The Poona Pact (1932) was an agreement between",
    answer: "Gandhi and Ambedkar",
    options: [
      "Nehru and Ambedkar",
      "Gandhi and Ambedkar",
      "Malaviya and Ambedkar",
      "Gandhi and Nehru"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following treaties brought an end to the independent existence of Peshwa Baji Rao-II?",
    answer: "Treaty of Bassein",
    options: [
      "The Treaty of Purandhar",
      "Convention of Wadgaon",
      "Treaty of Bassein",
      "Treaty of Salbai"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who started the first English newspaper in India?",
    answer: "J.A. Hickey",
    options: [
      "Bal Gangadhar Tilak",
      "Raja Rammohan Roy",
      "J.A. Hickey",
      "Lord William Bentinck"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The first woman to become a Chief Minister of any State in India was",
    answer: "Sucheta Kripalani",
    options: [
      "Nandini Satpathy",
      "Dr. J. Jayalalitha",
      "Sucheta Kripalani",
      "Ms. Mayawati"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Who is the author of Vande Mataram?",
    answer: "Bankim Chandra Chatterjee",
    options: [
      "Mahatma Gandhi",
      "Rabindranath Tagore",
      "Bankim Chandra Chatterjee",
      "Sarat Chandra Chatterjee"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who is regarded as as the father of modern India",
    answer: "Raja Ram Mohan Roy",
    options: [
      "Raja Ram Mohan Roy",
      "Swami Dayananda Saraswati",
      "Sri Aurobindo",
      "Bhagat Singh"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The most Important feature of the Government of India Act of 1919 was",
    answer: "All the above",
    options: [
      "enlargement of Indian Councils",
      "provision for direct election",
      "dyarchy in the Provinces",
      "All the above"
    ]
  },
];